# KIERAN WARWICK

Software Engineer ∼ Rungway

▼ me@kieranwarwick.dev kieranwarwick.dev

**\** 07446 861907 github.com/kw510

**Q** London, UK in /in/kieran-warwick

#### **SUMMARY**

Product-driven software engineer. Master of Computer Science with First Class. Worked two startups, both leading innovative projects improving the scale and stability of their platforms. Main expertise is event-driven architecture using Go microservices, over gRPC. Considered a generalist programmer.

SKILLS

Go, TypeScript/JavaScript, SQL, Python, Languages:

Haskell, Java, C++, C, HTML, CSS, LATEX

Technologies: GCP, Docker, gRPC, Microservices, Kuber-

netes, Pub/Sub

#### EXPERIENCE

03/2023 -Present

### **Software Engineer**

Rungway

· Worked on V3 of the platform, which is a whole redesign of the platform. Backend work involved taking 25 complex Java microservices (with shared libraries), and condensing them into 5 simple go microservices.

· Collaborated with the insights team to provide a data dashboard. This was a bespoke piece of work to provide data to certain clients.

GCP / Go / gRPC / Pubsub / RabbitMQ / Java / React

11/2020 -03/2023

### **Software Engineer**

Thirdfort

- · Developed and maintained new consistent authorisation system, lead migration of the platform to this new system. This improved GET requests by 47%, to an average of 50ms.
- · Built and maintained the billing component, enabling operations to charge clients for exactly what they used on the platform.
- Provided mentoring and coaching support to other members of the team.
- · Helped out on devops duties, such as CI/CD to the GCP K8 cluster, as well as managing Pub/Sub message topics and the subscriptions.
- Part of the SRE team to solve production issues, and to fix them as well.
- · Worked with product, operations, design, and support, to provide technical knowledge about the system. GCP / Go / gRPC / Pubsub / Kafka / Node / React

10/2017 -06/2018

#### **Taught Academic Representative**

The University of Bath

- · Gathered and represented students' opinions of the course upon Staff Student Liaison Committees.
- · Relayed outcomes to both students and the SU, acting as a bridge of communication.
- · Negotiated upon the SSLC for higher marks for students who took a calculator exam paper, where a printing error caused no calculators to be provided.

10/2017 -06/2018

#### **Academic Peer Mentor**

The University of Bath

· Mentored a small group of first year students, helping them with their studies and adjusting to university.

### **PROJECTS**

Technology

# protoc-gen-go-mock (protoc plugin)

Medium / Github

A tool that generates Go language bindings of services in protobuf definition files used mocking gRPC in diffrent frameworks. Built because mocking gRPC frameworks should as easy as generating pb.go files.

Technology

# Analysis of Extended-Precision upon GPUs

Uses two floats to estimate a double, with arithmetic operations. Provides a speedup of up to 1.2 on consumer GPUs when compared to a native double.

# **EDUCATION**

**Master of Computer Science** 2016 - 2020

University of Bath

Graduated with a First Class with Honours

2013 - 2016 A-Levels Maths: A\*, Further Maths: A, Physics A Chichester High Schools' Sixth Form

2011 - 2013

Chichester High School for Boys

6As, 3Bs, 3Cs - including Maths & English

### INTERESTS